export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "What is financial literacy?",
    optionA: "The ability to read finance articles",
    optionB: "The ability to use knowledge and skills to make effective and informed money management decisions",
    optionC: "The ability to write good finance articles",
    optionD: "The ability to have a good budget",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following type of account is a deposit at a bank or savings and loan that pays interest, but cannot be withdrawn in check writing?",
    optionA: "Savings Account",
    optionB: "Checkings Account",
    optionC: "Burner Account",
    optionD: "Retirement Account",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Which federal loan type is not based on need and students are responsible for paying the interest on this loan while they are enrolled in college?",
    optionA: "Federal Unsubsidized Student Loan",
    optionB: "Federal Subsidized Student Loan",
    optionC: "Federal Unsubsidized Stafford Loan",
    optionD: "Federal Subsidized Stafford Loan",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Which federal loan type is available to students who are enrolled at least half-time that has a fixed interest rate established each year?",
    optionA: "Federal Unsubsidized Student Loan",
    optionB: "Federal Subsidized Student Loan",
    optionC: "Federal Unsubsidized Stafford Loan",
    optionD: "Federal Subsidized Stafford Loan",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which federal loan type is a low-interest loan awarded to exceptionally needy students and repayment of the loan begins nine months after a student is no longer enrolled in college at least half-time?",
    optionA: "Federal Perkins Loan",
    optionB: "Federal Undergraduate Loan",
    optionC: "Federal Subsidized Student Loan",
    optionD: "Federal Unsubsidized Student Loan",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a tool for getting money loaned to you by the company issuing the card, which must be paid back to the company monthly?",
    optionA: "Charge Card",
    optionB: "Credit Card",
    optionC: "Prepaid Card",
    optionD: "Debit Card",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a tool for getting money where you're given a short-term loan for one month; the only difference is that you must pay your bill in full at the end of each month and you cannot carry over any debt from one month to the next?",
    optionA: "Charge Card",
    optionB: "Credit Card",
    optionC: "Prepaid Card",
    optionD: "Debit Card",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a tool where money is immediately taken out of (subtracted from) your checking account?",
    optionA: "Charge Card",
    optionB: "Credit Card",
    optionC: "Prepaid Card",
    optionD: "Debit Card",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: `Which of the following best describes the measure used by credit card companies to determine if someone applying for a credit card is "credit worthy" (likely to repay) where an applicant with a low credit score may be denied credit?`,
    optionA: "Expense Report",
    optionB: "Credit History",
    optionC: "Credit Score",
    optionD: "Annual Assets",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes the record of how timely and completely a person has paid off credit in the past?",
    optionA: "Expense Report",
    optionB: "Credit History",
    optionC: "Credit Score",
    optionD: "Annual Assets",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following is not true about account numbers?",
    optionA: "Each bank account has a unique account number",
    optionB: "The account number can't be found at the bottom of a check",
    optionC: "The second set of numbers at the bottom of a check that tells the bank cashing the check which account to pull the money from",
    optionD: "The account number and routing number are the same",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "A budget can be best described as",
    optionA: "A set plan for coordinating income and expenses in a way that ensures you're left with sufficient money to cover your expenses",
    optionB: "A fixed income",
    optionC: "A fixed payment plan towards one's bills",
    optionD: "A balance in one's bank account",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes identity theft?",
    optionA: "Not a joke, Jim!",
    optionB: "Copying actions from another person and aligning them as your own",
    optionC: "A crime committed by stealing another person's identity information, assuming that person's identity, and using that stolen identity to make financial transactions",
    optionD: "A felony",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a retirement account offered through an employer, where an employee can contribute money from their paycheck before or after taxes?",
    optionA: "401K",
    optionB: "Roth IRA",
    optionC: "Mortgage",
    optionD: "Certificate of Deposit",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following is not a benefit of a 529 plan?",
    optionA: "Returns grow tax free",
    optionB: "Easy to maintain",
    optionC: "Investments can double within a year",
    optionD: "Can be used nationwide",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "A cash advance is",
    optionA: "a loan of cash you obtain with a credit card",
    optionB: "a faster way of cashing in checks",
    optionC: "a faster way of getting cash from ATMs",
    optionD: "a way of safely advancing cash to another user",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a type of savings vehicle in which you put your money away for a certain amount of time to allow your principal to earn interest?",
    optionA: "401K",
    optionB: "Roth IRA",
    optionC: "Mortgage",
    optionD: "Certificate of Deposit",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following types of accounts best describes a bank account that allows a customer to deposit and withdraw money and write checks?",
    optionA: "Money Market Account",
    optionB: "Checkings Account",
    optionC: "Roth IRA",
    optionD: "Certificate of Deposit",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a bank card that automatically deducts the amount of a purchase from the checking account of the cardholder?",
    optionA: "Charge Card",
    optionB: "Credit Card",
    optionC: "Prepaid Card",
    optionD: "Debit Card",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a report on a person's creditworthiness that includes identifying information, credit cards, late payments, bankruptcies, and savings balances?",
    optionA: "Credit Score",
    optionB: "Credit Card",
    optionC: "Credit Report",
    optionD: "Expense Report",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a payroll deduction collected by employers by law and sent to the federal government to support governmental programs?",
    optionA: "Federal Income Tax",
    optionB: "Social Security Tax",
    optionC: "State Unemployment Tax",
    optionD: "Local Income Tax",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes a retirement account designed for individual savers that offers tax savings, but as contribution limits and withdrawal restrictions?",
    optionA: "401K",
    optionB: "Roth IRA",
    optionC: "Mortgage",
    optionD: "Certificate of Deposit",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "A mortgage can be described as",
    optionA: "A loan to cover college expenses",
    optionB: "A loan to put towards the purchase of stocks",
    optionC: "A loan to pay off credit card bills",
    optionD: "A loan to purchase a home or other real estate",
    answer: "D"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following terms best describes interest which is calculated not only on the initial principal but also the accumulated interest of prior periods",
    optionA: "Monthly Interest",
    optionB: "Annual Interest",
    optionC: "Compound Interest",
    optionD: "Simple Interest",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes an open-ended fund operated by an investment company which raises money from shareholders and invests in group assets, in accordance with a stated set of objectives?",
    optionA: "Mutual Fund",
    optionB: "Mortgage",
    optionC: "Stock",
    optionD: "Bond",
    answer: "A",
  },
];

// Sources:
// https://quizlet.com/516960337/financial-literacy-quiz-questions-flash-cards/
// https://quizlet.com/76279408/financial-literacy-flash-cards/
// https://quizlet.com/62515839/everfi-flash-cards/